Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Journal entries, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 26/8)
    Vida Chenoweth handwritten journal entries and expenses list. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain Province, Mangseng, Rabaul. Vanuatu. June 8 and 12, 1986. May 23, 1996. June 10, 1997.
  - Edited journal entry, 1988 (Box-folder 26/9)
    Edited typed journal entries. May 22-29, 1988.
  - LOC 89.2bb, 1970 (Box-folder 26/10)
    Outline compiled from field trip, Ethnomusicology seminar, Norman SIL.
  - LOC 35f, 1990 (Box-folder 26/11)
    Notes from 1990 journal, Vida Chenoweth, Borneo expedition. June 15-23, 1990. See box 9, folder 26 for cross reference.
  - LOC 31.9, 1980 (Box-folder 26/12)
    Central Buang Poetry. Bruce A. Hooley. Sengii transcriptions by Vida Chenoweth. Observations from a preliminary analysis of Buang data by Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Buang. 1980-1983.
  - LOC 31.10, 1993 (Box-folder 26/13)
    Ethnomusicology field trip notes. Papua New Guinea, Kombio, Menya, Mbula checks. Jun 4-July 4, 1993.
  - LOC 34, 1991 (Box-folder 26/14)
    Notes from field trip with Wheaton Interns.
  - LOC 35, 1988 (Box-folder 26/15)
    Expedition diary. Original notes from 1988 expedition to Irian Jaya. West Papua, Irian Jaya. June 1988.
  - LOC 35ff, 1990 (Box-folder 26/16)
    Handwritten journal of Vida Chenoweth. Indonesida, Borneo, East Kalimantan. June 1990.
  - LOC 36 and 37, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 26/17)
    Tolai Phonemic Statement. Tape contents. By Beth Gathman and Denise Buikema. New Ireland.
  - LOC 37c (Box-folder 26/18)
    Emic analysis and transcriptions. Kara, New Ireland.
  - LOC 37.3b, 37.4b, 1986 (Box-folder 26/19)
    Excerpts from Baining Fire Dance. An Emic Analysis of the Baining Music System. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain Province, Baining language. June, 1986.
  - LOC 48b-c, 49.6a, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 26/20)
    Ethnomusicology field trip diaries. Papua New Guinea. May-June, 1992. June 1993.
  - Song contents list, 1984 (Box-folder 26/21)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons Province. Jun 28, July 3, 1984.
  - Tolai Transcriptions and Preliminary Analysis, c76/082, c76/083 (Box-folder 26/22)
    Transcriptions and Analysis of Tolai songs by 3 students: Beth Gathman, Denise Buikema, and Denise Darling. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain Province.
  - Field notebook, 1990 (Box-folder 26/23)
    Field Notebook. E. Kalimantan.
  - LOC 22.4, 1987 (Box-folder 26/24)
    Field Notebook. By Vida Chenoweth. Kenya. June, 1987.
  - Portions of Field Notebooks, 1986, 1993 (Box-folder 26/25)
    Portions of small field notebooks. Various locations and dates. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Tolai; Duke of York; Buka. June, 1986. June, 1993.
  - LOC 31.1, 31.6, 1967, 1991 (Box-folder 26/26)
    Song contents list and excerpts from journal of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. February, 1967 and June 11-12, 1991.
  - LOC 18.1 (Box-folder 26/27)
    Kosena song trascriptions.
  - Waffa Songs and Belau Art Exhibition, 1969, 1980 (Box-folder 27/1)
    Waffa Songs. Transcription of tape recorded in the village of Kusing in August 1969. Program for Belau Art Exhibition as part of the 3rd South Pacific Festival of Arts. Papua New Guinea. 1980.
  - Siane Communion Hymn, 1968 (Box-folder 27/2)
    Transcriptions of Siane Hymns.
  - Songs and Hymn Transcriptions (Box-folder 27/3)
    11 songs taped by David Strange, transcribed by Stephen Spike under direction of Vida Chenoweth. E.H.D, Papua New Guinea, Upper Asaro tribe.
  - Asaro Song Transcription Notebook (Box-folder 27/4)
    Song transcriptions and notes. Transcribed by Stephen Spike under direction of Vida Chenoweth. E.H.D, Papua New Guinea, Upper Asaro tribe.
  - Gahuku songs, 1970 (Box-folder 27/5)
    Gahuku songs and piece of correspondence. Goroka. Jan. 18, 1970.
  - 1993 Diary of Vida Chenoweth, 1993 (Box-folder 27/6)
    1993 Diary of Vida Chenoweth. References Cited from, A Perspective on Australian Aboriginal Ethnomusicology. Stephen Wild. Papua New Guinea, East Sepik Province.
  - An Approach to the Traditional Music of Papua New Guinea, 1973 (Box-folder 27/7)
    By students of Goroka Teachers College. January, 1973.
  - Analysis of the Musical System of the People of Western Samoa, 1986 (Box-folder 27/8)
    Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in candidacy for a liberal arts degree with the possible concentration in the field of medicine. By Lawrence Wesley Fountain. Wheaton, Illinois. February 27, 1986.
  - Notes and Programs on Various Aspects of Pacific Arts Festivals, 1980-2000 (Box-folder 27/9)
    Palau/Belau art exhibition. Newspaper clippings of Manus Island dancer. Report to Board of Governors identifying PNG performers. Program of events. First overseas performance of Tuvalu dancers. Student paper on Western Samoa. 2000 festival program of events in diglot of English and French.
  - Garland Encyclopedia Entries, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27/10)
    Articles by Vida Chenoweth in Volume 9 of The Garland Encyclopedia of World Music about music of the South Pacific. Original control number: LOC 55.11, LOC 49.10aaa. Vanuatu, Tanna Island/Mota Island. August 1994-August 1995.
  - Chenoweth diary, 1983 (Box-folder 27/11)
    Handwritten diary of Vida Chenoweth. March-July 1983.
  - Usarufa New Testament, 1980 (Box-folder 27/12)
    Translation of the New Testament into the Usarufa language. Published in 1980 by Park Press. South Holland, Ill.
  - Wewak Festival of the Arts, 1980 (Box-folder 27/13)
    Wewak Festival of the Arts. South Pacific Festival of Arts. Papua New Guinea. June-July, 1980.
  - Essentials for Translation, 1967-09 (Box-folder 27/14)
    By Darlene Bee. Part II, Anthropology Data.
  - The Music of the Usarufas, Part I, 1974 (Box-folder 28/1)
    A Thesis for the Degree of Doctor of Philosophy in Muisc. By Vida Chenoweth. University of Auckland. 220 pages. August 1974.
  - The Music of the Usarufas, Part II, 1997 (Box-folder 28/2)
    A Thesis for the Degree of Doctor of Philosophy in Muisc. By Vida Chenoweth. University of Auckland. October 1997.
  - Original Thesis, "The Music of the Usarufas" (with Appendix B) (folder 1 of 5), 1996 (Box-folder 28/3)
    By Vida Chenoweth for PhD degree. University of Auckland.
  - Original Thesis, "The Music of the Usarufas" (with Appendix B) (folder 2 of 5), 1996 (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Original Thesis, "The Music of the Usarufas" (with Appendix B) (folder 3 of 5), 1996 (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Original Thesis, "The Music of the Usarufas" (with Appendix B) (folder 4 of 5), 1996 (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Original Thesis, "The Music of the Usarufas" (with Appendix B) (folder 5 of 5), 1996 (Box-folder 29/3)
  - "The Music of the Usarufas," Appendix B Song Texts (folder 1 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 29/4)
  - "The Music of the Usarufas," Appendix B Song Texts (folder 2 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 29/5)
  - "The Music of the Usarufas," Appendix B Song Texts (folder 3 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 29/6)
  - Sound recording container documentation (Box-folder 30a/1-24)
    Photocopies of original sound recording containers.
  - Sound recording and moving image container documentation and accompanying documentation (Box-folder 30b/1-20)
    Photocopies of original sound recording containers and accompanying documentation.
  - Index cards for sound recordings (Box-folder 30c)
    Organized by geographic area and contains dates and technical details about recordings.
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  Note: Where gaps exist in SR numbering, these sound recordings are not accounted for in the collection. SR1001 - SR1089 are home-recorded lacquer discs, mostly of Vida Chenoweth's piano performances. Digital files are available within the range SR001-SR905, SR931-SR932, and SR1001-1089.
  - Simbu (Kukane Traditional music), ca. 1974, 1 sound cassette; C74/001 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR001)
    Institute of Papua New Guinea Studies. Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District; Recorded by Frederic Duvelle, 1974. Assistant Paul Kuange. Simbu (Kukane Traditional music) (track listing on cassette). Language group: Kukane. Content type: music. Field recording by Charles Duvelle, available for sale, bought by Chenoweth.
  - Music, Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C60; C82/002 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR002)
    Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District. Langauge/people: Golin. Original field recording.
  - Music, Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C60; C82/003 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR003)
  - Music, Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C90; C82/004 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR004)
    Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, Gumine Sub District, Chimbu Province. Langauge/people: Golin. Original field recording.
  - Music, Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C60; C82/005 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR005)
  - Music, Papua New Guinea, Chimbu District, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette, C60; C82/006 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR006)
  - Enga Traditional Music, 1974, 1 sound cassette; C74/007 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR007)
    Papua New Guinea, Enga Province. Enga Traditional Music. Institute of Papua New Guinea Studies (complete track listing on tape). Recorded by Frederic Duvelle, 1974. Assistant Kundapen Talyaga. Special call number: .953 Ins. T.1 c.1. Field recording by Charles Duvelle, available for sale, bought by Chenoweth.
  - Songs from Enga Province, ca. 1974, 1 sound cassette; C74/008 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR008)
    Papua New Guinea, Enga Province. Songs of courting ceremony, pan pipes, mourning song; Work song, love charm song (2), women's song, love song, initiation - baptism ceremony. Special call number: .953 Ins. T.1 c.2.
  - Songs from Enga Province, ca. 1974, 1 sound cassette; C74/008 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR009)
    Papua New Guinea, Enga Province. Enga traditional music from the Duvelle recording 1974, Side 2. Originally recorded by Frederic Duvelle. Copy of Duvelle commercial recording (C74/007).
  - Songs from Enga Province, ca. 1967, 1 sound cassette; C67/009 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR010)
    Papua New Guinea, Enga Province. Enga courtship songs.
  - Papua New Guinea, unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/010 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR011)
    Papua New Guinea.
  - Papua New Guinea, unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/011 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR012)
  - Songs from Enga Province, ca. 1967, 1 sound cassette; C67/012 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR013)
    Papua New Guinea, Enga Province. Sikita group. Duplicate. Contents: 5. Christmas Sing-sings, 10. Songs about the white men coming, 8. Pig exhchange sins-sings, 13. Courtship songs.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR014)
  - Music from Enga Province, ca. 1967, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR015)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1977, 1 sound tape reel; C77/015 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR016)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1977, 1 sound tape reel; R77/016 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR017)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1977, 1 sound tape reel; R77/017 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR018)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1978, 1 sound tape reel; R78/018 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR019)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1978, 1 sound cassette; R78/018 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR020)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1976, 1 sound tape reel; R76/019 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR021)
  - Music from the Western Province of Papua New Guinea, 1974, 1 sound cassette; R76/019 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR022)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/021 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR023)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound cassette, C60; R66/021 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR024)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound cassette; R66/021 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR025)
    Part II.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/022 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR026)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound cassette, C60; R66/022 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR027)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound cassette, C60; R66/022 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR028)
  - Maring songs and sing-sings from Papua New Guinea, ca. 1978, 1 sound cassette, C60; C78/023 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR029)
    Papua New Guinea, Western Highlands Province. Contents: 7 Maring songs recorded at Koinambe, WHP of Papua New Guinea by Vida Chenoweth. 3rd anniversary of PNG celebrated at Koinambe. Two sing-sings (gardening song, victory song). L Woodward. Special call number: .953 Mar. People/language group: Maring/Forest Maring. Original field recording.
  - Faiwol songs and stories, ca. 1971, 1 sound cassette, C60; C71/024 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR030)
    Papua New Guinea, Western Highlands Province. Songs and stories from Faiwol language. Music and spoken word. Original field recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1980, 1 sound tape reel; R80/025 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR031)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1978, 1 sound tape reel; R78/026 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR032)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1978, 1 sound tape reel; R78/027 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR033)
  - Music from Madang Province, Papua New Guinea, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/028 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR034)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1980, 1 sound tape reel; R80/029 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR035)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette, C90; R80/029 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR036)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; R80/029 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR037)
  - Kalam songs, 1982-06, 1 sound cassette; C82/030 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR038)
  - Kalam songs, 1982-06, 1 sound cassette; C82/030 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR039)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Contents: Kalam (Simbai, June 5, 1982) Scripture Song: MK 5:36. 6 Church Songs by Barnabus. Songs #7-11a Rom 5:8,9. Kalam (Simbai, June 5, 1982) Scripture Song: MK 5:36. 6 Church Songs by Barnabus. People/language group: Kalam. Music. Original field recording.
  - Kalam songs, 1982-06, 1 sound cassette; C82/031 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR040)
    Tape 1 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Kalam Songs for Worship (Simbai Madang Province, June 1982) continued from tape I. Tape II songs #11b-16; Kalam song of Kamep Wel category (a young man died before his time). People/language group: Kalam. Music. Original field recording. The two tapes assigned C82/031 appear to be exactly the same.
  - Kalam songs, 1982-06, 1 sound cassette; C82/031 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR041)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Contents: Kalam (Simbai, June 5, 1982) Scripture Song: MK 5:36. 6 Church Songs by Barnabus. Songs #7-11a Rom 5:8,9. Kalam (Simbai, June 5, 1982) Scripture Song: MK 5:36. 6 Church Songs by Barnabus. People/language: Kalam. Original field recording. The two tapes assigned C82/031 appear to be exactly the same.
  - Simbai songs, 1975, 1 sound cassette; C75/032 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR042)
    Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Music. Lyle Scholz. Simbai song tape. People/language: Kalam. Original field recording.
  - Music from Madang Province, Papua New Guinea, 1981, 1 sound cassette, C60; C81/033 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR043)
    Takia Bal (hymns) Rehburg Tape. Karkar Island. Music. Original field recording.
  - Kalam songs, 1976-05, 1 sound cassette, C60; C76/034 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR044)
    Tape 1 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Kalam Songs. People/language: Kalam. Original field recording.
  - Kalam songs, 1976-05, 1 sound cassette; C76/034 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR045)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Kalam Songs. People/language: Kalam. Original field recording. May be a copy of C75/033.
  - Scripture verses from Madang Province, Papua New Guinea, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette; C82/035 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR046)
    Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Scripture Verses Karam Lang. People/language: Kalam. Original field recording.
  - Kalam music and Chenoweth Wheaton College talk, ca. 1982, 1 sound cassette; C82/036 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR047)
    Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Karam Songs. Contents: Side A. Wheaton College Ethnomusicology Department. Dr. Chenoweth. Spoken word. People/language: Kalam. Wheaton college copy of original.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1975, 1 sound tape reel; R75/037 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR048)
  - Kobon songs, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette, C90; C80/038 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR049)
  - Kobon songs, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/038 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR050)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Kobon Church songs "Cassettes for Christ." First Church of the Nazarene, 2495 East Mountain Street, Pasadena, CA 91104, USA. Music. People/language group: Kobon. Note: It appears that Chenoweth recorded over a tape of Christian music from the United States during a workshop. This is indicated in the recording log and writing on the cassette.
  - Kobon songs, 1979-04, 1 sound cassette, C90; C79/039 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR051)
    Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Copy recorded by John Davies. Music. Special call number: .953 Kob t.4. People/language group: Kobon. Recorded by John Davies with Vida Chenoweth
  - Kobon songs, 1975, 1980, 1 sound cassette; C75/040, C80/040 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR052)
    Papua New Guinea, Madang Province. Kobon songs. Music. Special call number: .953 t.2. People/language group: Kobon. Copy from field recording. Side A includes parts of C79/039.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1968, 1 sound tape reel; R68/041 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR053)
    Special call number: .953 Ane.
  - Yagwoia traditional music, 1978-11, 1 sound cassette; C78/042 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR054)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Contents: Yagwoia Traditional Music. 1-12 Kanalčipu's Cousin (from Vailala). 126-222 Omeljamgwi 2, recorded at Palalye. People/language group: Yagwoia Language (Menyamya) Angan family. Collected by Mary Ruth and Hope Bowling.
  - Buang music, 1978-07-01, 1 sound cassette; C78/043 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR055)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Mumeng District. Music. People/language group: Buang Language. Dubbed from radio.
  - Buang music, 1971, 1 sound cassette; C71/044 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR056)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Mumeng District. Music. People/language group: Buang Language. Duplicate of field recording.
  - Buang music, 1971, 1 sound tape reel; C71/044 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR057)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Mumeng District. Music. Collected by Skai Kata (?). People/language group: Buang Language. Recording notes were in tape box.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1982, 1 sound tape reel; R82/045 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR058)
    Collected by Beth Gathman and Bruce Hooley. Master tape.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1982, 1 sound tape reel; R82/046 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR059)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1982, 1 sound tape reel; R82/047 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR060)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1982, 1 sound tape reel; R82/048 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR061)
  - Buang music, 1982-07, 1 sound cassette; C82/049 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR062)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, villages of Mapos, Mapos II, Humek. Collected by Beth Gathman and Bruce Hooley. Music. People/language group: Buong Language group. Duplicate. Reel #1. Copy of R82/045.
  - Buang music, 1982-07, 1 sound cassette; C82/050 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR063)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, villages of Humek, Sebulek, Seyuwee. Collected by Beth Gathman and Bruce Hooley. Music. People/language group: Buong Language group. Duplicate. Reel #2. Copy of R82/046.
  - Buang music, 1982-07, 1 sound cassette; C82/051 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR064)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, village of Seyuwee. Collected by Beth Gathman and Bruce Hooley. Music. People/language group: Buong Language group. Duplicate. Reel #3. Copy of R82/047.
  - Buang music, ca. 1975, 1 sound cassette, C60; C75/052 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR065)
    Tape 1 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Collected by Bruce Hooley. Music. Special call number: .953 Bua t.1. People/language group: Buang Language group. Original field recording.
  - Buang music, ca. 1975, 1 sound cassette, C60; C75/052 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR066)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Collected by Bruce Hooley. Music. Special call number: .953 Bua t.2. People/language group: Buang Language group. Original field recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/053, R67/054 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR067)
    Collected by Vida Chenoweth and Marge and Ray Dubert. Special call number: .953 Bia. Part of the same tape as R67/054.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/054 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR068)
    Collected by Vida Chenoweth and Marge and Ray Dubert. Special call number: .953 Bia.
  - Moimo mourning songs and Kipu visit, 1972, 1 sound cassette, C60; C73/055 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR069)
    Tape 1 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Moimo. Music/spoken word. Contents: Mourning Songs. Koitoi's Description of Kipu visit. Collected by Joan Coleman. Special call number: .953 Moi t. 1. People/language group: Kunimaipa. Original field recording.
  - Moimo mourning songs, 1977, 1 sound cassette, C90; C73/055 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR070)
    Tape 2 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Moimo Vi. Music/spoken word. Contents: Moimo Mourning songs. Collected by Joan Coleman. Special call number: .953 Moi t. 2. People/language group: Kunimaipa. Original field recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/056 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR071)
    Collected by Dorothy Price. Special call number: .953 Adz t.1, c.1; .953 Adz t.1 c.2.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/057a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR072)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; R69/057 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR073)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1970, 1 sound tape reel; R70/058 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR074)
    Collected by Dorothy Price.
  - Moimo religious songs, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/059 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR075)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Moimo Vi. Contents: Kunimaipa Hymns, Kunimaipa Church Songs. Music. Collected by Joan Coleman and Elaine Geary. People/language group: Kunimaipa. Original field recording.
  - Moimo religious songs, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/060, C80/061 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR076)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Moimo Vi. Contents: Kunimaipa Scripture Songs; Yele Scripture Songs (Rossel Island). Music. Special call number: .953 Kun t. 3. People/language group: Kunimaipa. Original field recording.
  - Moimo religious songs, ca. 1980, 1 sound cassette; C80/062 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR077)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Moimo Vi. Contents: Kunimaipa Scripture Songs. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Music. Special call number: .953 Kun t. 2. People/language group: Kunimaipa. Original field recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; R67/063 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR078)
    Collected by Vida Chenoweth, Dottie and Edie West. See also LOC 32.
  - Mor-Lae show, ca. 1966, 1 sound cassette; R66/064, R66/565a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR079)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province, Lae. Contents: Originally R66/565a, Mor-Lae Show. Music. Copy of reel on Wheaton College Tape.
  - Yele songs, ca. 1976, 1 sound cassette, C60; C76/065 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR080)
    Tape 1 of 2. Papua New Guinea, Milne Bay. Contents: Yele Songs, Rossel Island. Special call number: .953 Yel t.1. Music. People/language group: Yele. Original field recording.
  - Yele songs, ca. 1976, 1 sound cassette; C76/065 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR081)